I've made some changes to your marketing plan.
我做了一些改动 对你的市场营销计划.
I hope you don't mind.
我希望你不会介意.
No, of course not. It was very helpful.
No, 当然不会. 很有帮助.
I want to get things right.
我想把事情做好.
Easier said than done.
说比做容易.
Oh, Yes. Sometimes  it feels like we're in"Ho-Ho-Hotel".
Oh,Yes.有时候 感觉我们就像在"Ho-Ho-Hotel"里
Have you ever seen that film?
你看过那个电影吗?
Oh, I love that movie.
Oh, 我喜爱那个电影.
Remember the bellhop?
记得那个旅馆的服务员吗?
He keeps thinking he can smell cheese.
他一直觉得他能闻到奶酪味儿.
And he sniffs the guests.
他还对着客人们嗅来嗅去.
I like the way the chambermaids put crumbs in the beds of people they don't like.
我喜欢 女服务员们把面包屑放在她们不喜欢的客人床上.
-Oh! –And the guests can't sleep...
-Oh! -客人们不能入睡...
And they complain to the manager...
他们就向经理抱怨...
They can't sleep
他们不能入睡
because there are crumbs in the bed...
因为他们的床上有面包屑...
And he says "Stop eating in bed."
而他说"不要在床上吃东西."
Oh, well at least we don't have those problems!
Oh,well 至少我们还没有那种问题!
Suddenly our situation looks much better,
突然之间我们的情形看上去好多了,
doesn't it?
不是吗?